life is a journey filled with wishes and
dreams
you nurture the aspirations of your
loved ones
you tick off goals from your bucket list
you pave the way
towards a better future for your family
and the list goes on
however in this journey of life nothing
is certain
you may come across situations for which
you haven't prepared
therefore you need a plan which gives
you the guarantee to fulfill your small
and big dreams
no matter what presenting
icing guaranteed income for tomorrow
a sure short way to plan for your dreams
today
so they are fulfilled tomorrow it also
offers a host of
other unique benefits you can choose
from different options to receive your
money
early income option get income
immediately from second year onwards
you will also receive a higher
guaranteed income
one year after your premium payment term
income option get guaranteed income for
five
seven or ten years after two years on
completion of your premium payment
term both income and early income
options have a special stay to date
feature that allows you to receive money
on a fixed date every year so now you
can receive your guaranteed income on a
special date like your birthday or
anniversary
lump sum option single pay pay only once
and get a guaranteed lump sum amount to
fulfill your dreams after 5
10 or 15 years you also get a life cover
to protect the future of your family
what's more you can also avail tax
benefits on premiums paid and maturity
proceeds
so what are you waiting for now achieve
your dreams with a gift of guarantee